<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MoeTranslate</string>
    <string name="floating_ball_menu_1">Floating Ball Menu</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_label">MoeTranslator Translate Service</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">[Function Description] \nEnable accessibility permissions to take screenshots for translation.\nWhen granting permissions, a warning will pop up. Please rest assured that Mengyi will not collect any of your information.</string>
    <string name="translate_page">Translate</string>
    <string name="gemini_page">Gemini</string>
    <string name="madoka_page">Madoka</string>
    <string name="me_page">Settings</string>
    <string name="api_name">API：%s</string>
    <string name="tencent_cloud">Tencent Cloud</string>
    <string name="baidu_translate">Baidu Translate</string>
    <string name="android_sdk_old_title">Android version is too low</string>
    <string name="android_sdk_old_content">It looks like your Android version is less than Android 11 (API 30) or Harmony OS version is less than 3.0, which means that you cannot use the translation function of this software, but you can still use other functions except translation. If you want to experience all the functions of this software, please upgrade the system or change the device.</string>
    <string name="user_known">OK</string>
    <string name="find_new_version">New version found</string>
    <string name="version_name">New Version：</string>
    <string name="ignore_update">Ignore this version</string>
    <string name="go_to_update">Go to update</string>
    <string name="not_update">Not yet</string>
    <string name="update_prompt">Do you want to update now? Click Update to jump to the official website of MoeTranslate. Click Download on the official website to get the latest version.</string>
    <string name="getting_notification">Getting notifications…</string>
    <string name="nllb_not_download_content">It looks like you have selected NLLB as the translation model, but it seems that the NLLB model file has not been downloaded yet, so translation is not possible. Click Go to Download to enter the download page; of course, you can also choose other translation APIs to use the translation function.</string>
    <string name="go_to_download">Go to Download</string>
    <string name="nllb_not_download_title">NLLB model file not downloaded</string>
    <string name="user_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="api_not_config_content">It looks like you have selected %s as the translation API, but it seems that you have not configured it yet, so translation is not possible. Click Config to enter the API settings page; of course, you can also select other translation APIs to use the translation function.</string>
    <string name="api_not_config_title">Translation API not configured</string>
    <string name="go_to_config">Config</string>
    <string name="custom_api_not_config_content">It looks like you have used a custom translation API, but it seems that you have not configured it yet, so translation is not possible. Click Config to enter the API settings page; of course, you can also choose other translation APIs to use the translation function.</string>
    <string name="not_accessibility_service_title">Accessibility permissions not granted</string>
    <string name="not_accessibility_service_content">It seems that you have not granted MoeTranslate accessibility permissions. Screenshot Translation requires accessibility permissions to take screenshots. Click to grant accessibility permissions to grant the app.\n\nThe specific authorization path varies slightly on devices of different brands, roughly:\n<b>General tab → Downloaded apps → Find \"MoeTranslateTranslation Service\" → Use \"MoeTranslate Translation Service\".</b>\nWhen granting permissions, a warning will pop up. Please rest assured that MoeTranslate will not collect any of your information.</string>
    <string name="go_to_grant">Grant</string>
    <string name="not_floating_title">Floating window permission not granted</string>
    <string name="not_floating_content">It seems that you have not granted MoeTranslate floating window permission. Screenshot Translation needs to obtain floating window permission to display the floating ball anytime and anywhere. Click to grant to grant the app floating window permission. \n\nThe specific authorization path is roughly: \n<b>find MoeTranslate in the list → grant MoeTranslate the permission to display on top of other applications.</b></string>
    <string name="not_notify_title">Notification permission not granted</string>
    <string name="not_notify_content">It seems that you have not granted MoeTranslate notification permission. Screenshot Translation requires notification permission. Click Grant to grant the app notification permission.</string>
    <string name="select_source_language">Select source language</string>
    <string name="select_target_language">Select target language</string>
    <string name="custom_api_select_language">Custom</string>
    <string name="source_language">Source Language：</string>
    <string name="target_language">Target Language：</string>
    <string name="getting_update">Checking for updates…</string>
    <string name="no_update">Already the latest version</string>
    <string name="internet_error">Network Error, please check and try again</string>
    <string name="get_notification_error">Failed to get notification, maybe the network is not connected</string>
    <string name="translation_mode">Translation Mode</string>
    <string name="api_configuration">API Configuration</string>
    <string name="personalization_setting">Personalization</string>
    <string name="article_page">One Day · One Article</string>
    <string name="faq_title">FAQ</string>
    <string name="error_code">Error Code</string>
    <string name="check_update">Check for Updates</string>
    <string name="clear_cache">Clear the Cache</string>
    <string name="about_page">About</string>
    <string name="choose_mode">Select the translation mode you wish to use</string>
    <string name="ocr_mode">Local OCR Recognition + Text Translation<font color="#E25A5C">(Recommended)</font></string>
    <string name="ocr_mode_description">Perform offline OCR locally to extract text from the image, and then translate the text. Supports local AI offline text translation, as well as the use of preset cloud text translation APIs and custom cloud text translation APIs. Note that offline OCR recognition only supports Chinese, Japanese, and English. This method consumes very little data traffic; if you choose to process it completely locally, you can even do it completely offline.</string>
    <string name="pic_mode">Upload Images Directly for Translation</string>
    <string name="pic_mode_description">Upload the screenshot directly to the cloud API for translation. It supports using the preset cloud image translation API, and also supports using the custom cloud image translation API. <font color="#E25A5C">It does not support local translation</font>. This method consumes relatively more data traffic.</string>
    <string name="mlkit_name">ML Kit</string>
    <string name="mlkit_description">Google\'s machine learning kit runs on the device and is suitable for casual and simple translation. <font color="#E25A5C">You need to download a model file of about 100MB for the first run</font>. After the download is complete, you can use it right away without the need for a network connection. Click \"Manage ML Kit model files\" below to download and delete model files.</string>
    <string name="nllb_name">NLLB Translate Model</string>
    <string name="nllb_description">Meta\'s model, which is designed for translation, is called \"No Language Left Behind\". As the name suggests, it supports multiple languages. The translation effect of this model is better, but it also needs to be downloaded before use. <font color="#E25A5C">When running for the first time, you need to download a model file of about 1GB. At the same time, the device needs to have at least 6GB of RAM to use this model</font>. After the download is complete, there is no need for a network connection, and it can be used immediately. Click \"Manage NLLB model files\" below to download and delete model files.</string>
    <string name="manage_nllb_models">Manage NLLB Model Files</string>
    <string name="baiduapi_name">Baidu Translate</string>
    <string name="baiduapi_description">Baidu Translate\'s API, click \"Manage Baidu Translate API\" below to set up the API, and you can also view the API application tutorial (there is a free call quota of 1 million characters per month).</string>
    <string name="tencentapi_description">Tencent Cloud\'s translation API, click \"Manage Tencent Cloud API\" below to set up the API, and you can also view the API application tutorial (there is a free call quota of 5 million characters per month).</string>
    <string name="tencentapi_name">Tencent Cloud</string>
    <string name="ai_title">Local AI Translation</string>
    <string name="pre_api_title">Pre-Configured Cloud API</string>
    <string name="custom_api_text_title"><font color="#E25A5C">(Advanced settings)</font> Customize the Cloud Text Translation API</string>
    <string name="custom_api_text_1">Custom cloud <font color="#E25A5C">text</font> translation API1</string>
    <string name="custom_api_text_2">Custom cloud <font color="#E25A5C">text</font> translation API2</string>
    <string name="custom_api_text_3">Custom cloud <font color="#E25A5C">text</font> translation API3</string>
    <string name="manage_baidu_api">Manage Baidu Translate API</string>
    <string name="manage_tencent_api">Manage Tencent Cloud API</string>
    <string name="manage_custom_api_text_1">Manage custom cloud text translation API1</string>
    <string name="manage_custom_api_text_2">Manage custom cloud text translation API2</string>
    <string name="manage_custom_api_text_3">Manage custom cloud text translation API3</string>
    <string name="current_mode_text">Current Translation Mode：Local OCR Recognition + Text Translation</string>
    <string name="current_mode_pic">Current Translation Mode：Upload Images Directly for Translation</string>
    <string name="custom_api_pic_title"><font color="#E25A5C">(Advanced settings)</font> Customize the Cloud Image Translation API</string>
    <string name="custom_api_pic_1">Custom cloud <font color="#E25A5C">image</font> translation API1</string>
    <string name="custom_api_pic_2">Custom cloud <font color="#E25A5C">image</font> translation API2</string>
    <string name="custom_api_pic_3">Custom cloud <font color="#E25A5C">image</font> translation API3</string>
    <string name="manage_custom_api_pic_1">Manage custom cloud image translation API1</string>
    <string name="manage_custom_api_pic_2">Manage custom cloud image translation API2</string>
    <string name="manage_custom_api_pic_3">Manage custom cloud image translation API3</string>
    <string name="no_less_one">Please select an option</string>
    <string name="small_ram_title">RAM is less than 6GB</string>
    <string name="small_ram_content">It looks like you have selected NLLB as the translation API, but it seems that your device has less than 8G of RAM, which may cause problems when inferring the model. Please rest assured that the program will not prevent you from using the model, but there is no guarantee that there will be no accidents when the RAM is less than 6G.</string>
    <string name="custom_api_select_language_title">Custom API does not support language selection</string>
    <string name="custom_api_select_language_content">It looks like you are using a custom translation API. In this case, you should not use MoeTranslate to select the source and target languages. Instead, you should write the source and target languages ​​into the API because MoeTranslate does not know the language codes specified by your custom API (some API providers do not use BCP-47 codes as their language codes).</string>
    <string name="whatsthis">What\'s this?</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="baidu_hint_account">APP ID</string>
    <string name="baidu_hint_secret_key">SecretKey</string>
    <string name="tencent_hint_account">SecretId</string>
    <string name="tencent_hint_secret_key">SecretKey</string>
    <string name="fill_blank">Please fill in the API information completely</string>
    <string name="save_successfully">Saved successfully</string>
    <string name="api_saved">（Encrypted storage）</string>
    <string name="view_tutorial">View Tutorial</string>
    <string name="go_now">Go Now</string>
    <string name="manage_mlkit_models">Manage ML Kit Model Files</string>
    <string name="mlkit_not_download_title">ML Kit model file not downloaded</string>
    <string name="mlkit_not_download_content">It looks like you have selected ML Kit as the translation model, but it seems that the ML Kit model file has not been downloaded yet, so translation cannot be performed. Click Go to Download to enter the download page. <font color="#E25A5C">The first run requires downloading a model file of about 100MB</font>, so it is recommended to download in a WIFI environment. After the download is complete, there is no need for a network, and it can be used immediately.</string>
    <string name="startup_success">Startup successfully</string>
    <string name="startup_failure">Startup failed：%s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_recycle">The accessibility permission has been reclaimed by the system. You can re-grant the relevant permission in the tutorial in the upper right corner of the homepage.</string>
    <string name="floating_ball_menu_2">Floating Ball Menu</string>
    <string name="floating_ball_menu_3">Floating Ball Menu</string>
    <string name="repeat_crop">Cannot open the selection box repeatedly</string>
    <string name="repeat_textview">Cannot enter the translation result adjustment state repeatedly</string>
    <string name="textview_first">Please adjust the translation result position first</string>
    <string name="crop_first">Please select the screenshot area first</string>
    <string name="finish_textview">Adjustment completed</string>
    <string name="initialization_start">Start model initialization, please start using translation after initialization is completed...</string>
    <string name="initialization_complete">Model initialization completed</string>
    <string name="initialization_failed">Model initialization failed, possibly due to insufficient memory.</string>
    <string name="initialization_not_complete">The model has not been initialized and the translation function cannot be used.</string>
    <string name="finish_crop">Selection completed</string>
    <string name="not_added_remove">The translation result view has not been added and does not need to be removed.</string>
    <string name="orientation_changed">Screen orientation change detected, please reselect the screenshot area</string>
    <string name="download_tips">In this page, you can download the NLLB model file. In order to keep the download process uninterrupted, please <font color="#E25A5C">do not leave this page while downloading</font>. Since the file is hosted in Cloudflare R2, it may not be available for download depending on network conditions. You can flexibly switch between Wi-Fi and data traffic, and enable or disable the VPN.\n</string>
    <string name="download_manually">If the file cannot be downloaded in any case, please <font color="#2474b5">click here</font> to see how to download it manually.</string>
    <string name="start_download">Start Download</string>
    <string name="delete_models">Delete Models</string>
    <string name="stop_download">Stop Downloading</string>
    <string name="get_download_info_error">Failed to get download information：%s</string>
    <string name="download_files_prompt">The following %d files will be downloaded in turn:</string>
    <string name="download_total_size">Total Size：%s</string>
    <string name="download_start_tips">Download tips</string>
    <string name="download_failed">Download Failed：%s</string>
    <string name="download_pause">The download has been stopped</string>
    <string name="current_download">Downloading：%s  %d/%d</string>
    <string name="verify_file">Verifying file：%s</string>
    <string name="delete_download">All files deleted</string>
    <string name="delete_download_failed">Failed to delete folder：%s</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait</string>
    <string name="get_download_info">Getting download information...</string>
    <string name="nllb_status_download">NLLB model download status: Downloaded</string>
    <string name="nllb_status_not_download">NLLB model download status: Not downloaded</string>
    <string name="mlkit_download_tips">In this page, you can download ML Kit model files. In order to keep the download process from being interrupted, please <font color="#E25A5C">do not leave this page while downloading</font>. Since the model file is stored on Google\'s server, and the download operation is encapsulated in the ML Kit library, it cannot be controlled separately. Therefore, the download may not be possible depending on the network conditions; please flexibly switch WLAN and data traffic, and enable Or turn off the VPN.\n\nSince the download operation is encapsulated in the ML Kit library, the download progress cannot be displayed in the software. The download operation will call the system downloader and the progress should be displayed in the notification bar. <font color="#E25A5C">The total size of the files to be downloaded is expected to be about 100MB</font>.</string>
    <string name="mlkit_status_download">ML Kit model download status: Downloaded</string>
    <string name="mlkit_status_not_download">ML Kit model download status: Not Downloaded</string>
    <string name="check_mlkit_download_error">Check status failed：%s</string>
    <string name="current_download_mlkit">Downloading：%s Language Model</string>
    <string name="is_translating">The last translation task is still in progress, please wait...</string>
    <string name="translation_failed">Translation Failed：%s</string>
    <string name="font_title">Font</string>
    <string name="font_summary">Current font：%s\nChoose a font you like</string>
    <string name="font_default">Follow the system</string>
    <string name="font_setting">Font settings</string>
    <string name="font_choose">Select font（ttf）</string>
    <string name="set_success">Setup successfully</string>
    <string name="font_failed">Font setting failed：%s</string>
    <string name="font_size_float">You can enter decimals</string>
    <string name="font_size_setting">Set font size</string>
    <string name="font_size_invalid">Please enter a valid number</string>
    <string name="font_size_summary">Current size：%s\nYou can enter decimals</string>
    <string name="font_size_title">Font Size</string>
    <string name="font_size_hint">Current size：%s</string>
    <string name="model_hasbeen_download_title">The model file has been downloaded</string>
    <string name="model_hasbeen_download_content">The model file has already been downloaded to your device, so there is no need to download it again. If you do need to re-download the model file, you can click \"Delete Models\" to re-download the model.</string>
    <string name="font_color">Font Color</string>
    <string name="font_color_summary">Choose a font color you like</string>
    <string name="result_background_color">Background Color</string>
    <string name="result_background_color_summary">Choose a background color that you like</string>
    <string name="penetrability">Permeability</string>
    <string name="penetrability_summary">When turned on, the translation result box will be transparent, but the transparency will increase</string>
    <string name="translate_result_box">Translation results box</string>
    <string name="merge_ocr">Merge multi-line OCR results</string>
    <string name="merge_ocr_summary">Current mode：%s\nThe default OCR result will split a piece of text into multiple lines, which greatly reduces the translation effect. It is recommended to choose \"Direct merging\" to get the best results in most cases</string>
    <string name="no_merge">No merging</string>
    <string name="segmented_merging">Segmented merging</string>
    <string name="direct_mergig">Direct mergig</string>
    <string name="show_source_text_title">Also show original text</string>
    <string name="show_source_text_summary">Current mode：%s\n(only available in OCR mode) displays the translation result and the original text after OCR</string>
    <string name="volcapi_name">Volc Engine</string>
    <string name="volcapi_description">Volc Engine API, click \"Manage Volc Engine API\" below to set up the API, and you can also view the API application tutorial (there is a free call quota of 2 million characters per month).</string>
    <string name="manage_volc_api">Manage Volc Engine API</string>
    <string name="niuapi_name">NiuTrans</string>
    <string name="niuapi_description">NiuTrans API, click \"Manage NiuTrans API\" below to set up the API, and you can also view the API application tutorial (there is a free call quota of 200,000 characters per day).</string>
    <string name="manage_niu_api">Manage NiuTrans API</string>
    <string name="baiduapi_description_pic">Baidu Translate\'s API, click \"Manage Baidu Translate API\" below to set up the API, and you can also view the API application tutorial (there are 10,000 free calls for image translation per month).</string>
    <string name="tencentapi_description_pic">Tencent Cloud\'s translation API,  click \"Manage Tencent Cloud API\" below to set up the API, and you can also view the API application tutorial (10,000 free calls for image translation per month).</string>
    <string name="volc_hint_account">Access Key ID</string>
    <string name="volc_hint_secret_key">Secret Access Key</string>
    <string name="whats_api_title">What is %s API</string>
    <string name="whats_api_content">MoeTranslate can use the APIs of different platforms to provide translation services, which means that you need to apply for APIs from the corresponding platform. The API platform you have now selected seems to be %1$s, click \"Go Now\" to start applying for %1$s API. For more information on how to apply for %1$s API, please click \"View Tutorial\". Please note that these APIs are free to apply for, and there are quite a few free calls per month.\n\nCompared with ML Kit and NLLB and other local model translations, the translation effect of using cloud APIs is undoubtedly better, so it is recommended that you use cloud APIs for translation when the network is good.</string>
    <string name="niu_hint_secret_key">API-KEY</string>
    <string name="niu_noneed">No need to fill in</string>
    <string name="floating_ball">Floating ball</string>
    <string name="floating_ball_pic_summary">Current image：%s\nChoose a floating ball icon you like, and the image aspect ratio is 1:1 to work better</string>
    <string name="floating_ball_pic_title">Floating Ball Icon</string>
    <string name="floating_ball_press_title">Long press determine time</string>
    <string name="floating_ball_press_summary">Current judgment time：%s ms\nPress and hold the floating ball, and the judgment time of the menu will pop up, in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="ball_setting">Floating ball icon</string>
    <string name="ball_icon_default">Restore default</string>
    <string name="pic_choose">Select picture（png/jpg）</string>
    <string name="default_name">Default</string>
    <string name="current_judgment_time">Current judgment time：%s ms</string>
    <string name="int_only">Enter an integer</string>
    <string name="introduce_custom_text_api_title">Custom Text Translation API Function Description</string>
    <string name="dont_konw_custom">😵Don\'t know what this is? Click me for tips.</string>
    <string name="request_method">Request Method</string>
    <string name="base_url">Base URL</string>
    <string name="headers">Headers</string>
    <string name="add_header">Add Header</string>
    <string name="json_body">JSON Body</string>
    <string name="add_json_field">Add JSON Field</string>
    <string name="query_parameters">Query Prameters</string>
    <string name="json_response_path">JSON Response Path</string>
    <string name="save_configuration">Save Configuration</string>
    <string name="add_query_parameter">Add Query Parameter</string>
    <string name="use_source_text">In the Value field, use \"usesourcetext\" to represent the text to be translated</string>
    <string name="use_img_base64">In the Value field, use \"useimgbase64\" to represent the base64 of the image to be translated.</string>
    <string name="use_img_file">In the Value field, use \"useimgfile\" to represent the image file to be translated.</string>
    <string name="request_body">Request Body</string>
    <string name="add_body_field">Add Body Field</string>
    <string name="introduce_custom_pic_api_title">Custom Image Translation API Function Description</string>
    <string name="introduce_custom_pic_api_content">\n⚠️ Note: <b>This is an advanced feature that requires you to have basic API call knowledge.</b>\n\n<big>1. Basic Description</big>\nThis feature allows you to configure your own <b>image translation API</b>, supporting both GET and POST request methods. (For image translation, the POST Content-Type can be either application/json; charset=utf-8 or multipart/form-data. Simply select the appropriate Content-Type in the dropdown menu, and there’s <b>no need</b> to explicitly add it to the request headers below.) All API responses must be in JSON format.\n\n<big>2. Usage Scenarios</big>\nTypically, major translation API providers implement their own signature algorithms, making it impossible to integrate via simple GET/POST requests. As such, the practical use case for the custom image translation API is to connect with a translation API interface that you’ve built yourself.\n\n<big>3. Parameter Description</big>\n1、Request Method: Can be either GET or POST.\n2、Content-Type (POST only): Can be application/json or multipart/form-data.\n3、Base URL: Can specify http or https. If no scheme is specified, the default is https.\n4、Query Parameters (GET only): Parameters appended to the base URL.\n5、Request Headers: Headers sent with the request.\n6、Request Body (POST only): Content included with the request.\n7、JSON Response Path: Path to retrieve the translation result from the API response JSON.\n\nNote:\n1、In \"Query Parameters\" and the request body with Content-Type set to application/json, <b>use \"useimgbase64\" to represent the image file to be translated</b>.\n2、In the request body with Content-Type set to multipart/form-data, <b>use \"useimgfile\" to represent the image file to be translated</b>.\n3、Additionally, ensure that both \"source language\" and \"target language\" codes are included in the \"Query Parameters\" or \"Request Body.\"\n\n<big>4. Request Examples</big>\n<b>GET Request</b>\nBase URL:\nhttps://api.example.com/translate\n\nQuery Parameters:\nKey: img, Value: useimgbase64\nKey: source, Value: ja\nKey: target, Value: zh\n\nRequest Headers:\nAuthorization = my_custom_token\n\n<b>POST Request</b>\nContent-Type:\napplication/json\n\nBase URL:\nhttps://api.example.com/translate\n\nRequest Headers:\nAuthorization = my_custom_token\n\nRequest Body:\nKey: img, Value: useimgbase64\nKey: source, Value: ja\nKey: target, Value: zh\n\n<b>POST Request</b>\nContent-Type:\nmultipart/form-data\n\nBase URL:\nhttps://api.example.com/translate\n\nRequest Headers:\nAuthorization = my_custom_token\n\nRequest Body:\nKey: img, Value: useimgfile\nKey: source, Value: ja\nKey: target, Value: zh\n\n<big>5. JSON Response Path</big>\n<b>Example 1:</b>\nSuppose the successful JSON response is as follows:\n\n{\n    \"code\": 0,\n    \"msg\": \"success\",\n    \"data\": {\n        \"translation\": \"Hello World\"\n    }\n}\n\nThen the JSON response path should be: \"data.translation\".\n\n<b>Example 2:</b>\nSuppose the successful JSON response is as follows:\n\n{\n    \"code\": 0,\n    \"msg\": \"success\",\n    \"result\": \"Hello World\"\n}\n\nThen the JSON response path should be: \"result\".(Excludes \".\")\n\n<big>6. Before Using This Feature</big>\nYou can first test the API response using tools like Postman or Reqable. Once the tests are successful, you can enter the relevant parameters into this feature.</string>
    <string name="introduce_not_show_again">Don\'t remind again</string>
    <string name="introduce_custom_text_api_content">\n⚠️ Note: <b>This is an advanced feature that requires you to have basic API call knowledge.</b>\n\n<big>1. Basic Description</big>\nThis feature allows you to configure your own <b>text translation API</b>, supporting both GET and POST request methods. (For text translation, the POST Content-Type must and can only be application/json; charset=utf-8. There’s <b>no need</b> to explicitly add it to the request headers, as it’s already preset.) All API responses must be in JSON format.\n\n<big>2. Usage Scenarios</big>\nTypically, major translation API providers implement their own signature algorithms, making it impossible to integrate via simple GET/POST requests. As such, the practical use case for the custom text translation API is to connect with a translation API interface that you’ve built yourself.\n\n<big>3. Parameter Description</big>\n1、Request Method: Can be either GET or POST.\n2、Base URL: Can specify http or https. If no scheme is specified, the default is https.\n3、Query Parameters (GET only): Parameters appended to the base URL.\n4、Request Headers: Headers sent with the request.\n5、JSON Request Body (POST only): JSON content included with the request.\n6、JSON Response Path: Path to retrieve the translation result from the API response JSON.\n\nNote:\n1、In \"Query Parameters\" and \"JSON Request Body,\" <b>use “usesourcetext” to represent the text to be translated</b>.\n2、Make sure to include both the \"source language\" and \"target language\" codes in the \"Query Parameters\" or \"JSON Request Body.\"\n3、Additionally, specify the \"source language\" in the main interface, as MoeTranslate requires the \"source language\" when performing OCR text recognition.\n\n<big>4. Request Examples</big>\n<b>GET Request</b>\nBase URL:\nhttps://api.example.com/translate\n\nQuery Parameters:\nKey: text, Value: usesourcetext\nKey: source, Value: ja\nKey: target, Value: zh\n\nRequest Headers:\nAuthorization = my_custom_token\n\n<b>POST Request</b>\nBase URL:\nhttps://api.example.com/translate\n\nRequest Headers:\nAuthorization = my_custom_token\n\nJSON Request Body:\nKey: text, Value: usesourcetext\nKey: source, Value: ja\nKey: target, Value: zh\n\n<big>5. JSON Response Path</big>\n<b>Example 1:</b>\nSuppose the successful JSON response is as follows:\n\n{\n    \"code\": 0,\n    \"msg\": \"success\",\n    \"data\": {\n        \"translation\": \"Hello World\"\n    }\n}\n\nThen the JSON response path should be: \"data.translation\".\n\n<b>Example 2:</b>\nSuppose the successful JSON response is as follows:\n\n{\n    \"code\": 0,\n    \"msg\": \"success\",\n    \"result\": \"Hello World\"\n}\n\nThen the JSON response path should be: \"result\".(Excludes \".\")\n\n<big>6. Before Using This Feature</big>\nYou can first test the API response using tools like Postman or Reqable. Once the tests are successful, you can enter the relevant parameters into this feature.</string>
    <string name="failed_save_config">Failed to save configuration：%s</string>
    <string name="key_value_blank">Key or value is blank</string>
    <string name="url_blank">URL cannot be blank</string>
    <string name="response_json_blank">JSON Response Path cannot be blank</string>
    <string name="gemini_intro">Gemini is Google\'s latest generative AI, and it\'s very easy to configure, but <font color="#E25A5C">if you\'re in China, you\'ll probably need a VPN to use it</font>. Click \"View Tutorial\" to see how to get Gemini\'s API.</string>
    <string name="gemini_key">Your Gemini API Key</string>
    <string name="gemini_title">Configure Gemini API</string>
    <string name="set_floating_ball_press">Set long press judgment time</string>
    <string name="delete_history_content">Are you sure you want to delete all your chats? This will also erase Gemini\'s memory.</string>
    <string name="delete_history_title">Delete chat history</string>
    <string name="confirm">Yes</string>
    <string name="delete_finish">The chat history has been cleared</string>
    <string name="gemini_api_empty">Gemini API has not been set up yet</string>
    <string name="gemini_thinking">🤔Thinking...</string>
    <string name="gemini_set_api">If you haven\'t configured the Gemini API yet, click the gear button in the upper left corner to do so, where you can also view the tutorial.</string>
    <string name="error_occurred">An error occurred：%s</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="say_something">Say something...</string>
    <string name="ocr">OCR</string>
    <string name="pic">Pic</string>
    <string name="custom">Custom</string>
    <string name="welcome_home_title">Ready to start translation</string>
    <string name="welcome_home_subtitle">Please configure the following options to start your translation journey</string>
    <string name="welcome_home_title_2">Translation Has Started！</string>
    <string name="welcome_home_subtitle_2">You can change the \"source/target\" language or stop the translation at any time</string>
    <string name="start_ball">Let’s get started！</string>
    <string name="stop_ball">I want to stop！</string>
    <string name="stop_success">Stop successfully</string>
    <string name="stop_failed">Stop failed：%s</string>
    <string name="textview_tip">The translation result will be displayed here, please be careful not to coincide with the position of the original text, so as not to affect the translation of the screenshot.</string>
    <string name="cache_content">MoeTranslate caches up to the last 200 screenshots when it is translated, and it will be overwritten when the screenshots are greater than 200, and these screenshots are saved in the Android/data/com.moe.moetranslator/cache/screenshots folder, which you can view in the file management at any time. Generally speaking, these screenshots won\'t take up much space, and of course, you can also choose to clear these cache data now.</string>
    <string name="clear_cache_success">Clear successfully</string>
    <string name="clear_cache_failed">Clear failed</string>
    <string name="keep_cache">Reserved for now</string>
    <string name="still_running">The Translation Floatingball seems to be still running, so please turn it off before adjusting the settings</string>
    <string name="invalid_combination">The source language and the target language are the same, which is a meaningless translation combination</string>
    <string name="bingapi_name">Bing Translate</string>
    <string name="bingapi_description">The translation API can be used without configuring a key, and is implemented by simulating a browser accessing Bing Translate for the web. <font color="#E25A5C">This method relies on the structure of the web page and the extraction of tokens, which is less stable and may be subject to access restrictions, so please use other translation APIs more</font>.</string>
    <string name="azureapi_name">Azure AI Translate</string>
    <string name="azureapi_description">Microsoft Azure AI Translator API, click \"Manage Azure API\" below to set up the API, and you can also view the API application tutorial (there is a free call quota of 2 million characters per month).</string>
    <string name="manage_azure_api">Manage Azure API</string>
    <string name="azure_hint_secret_key">KEY（1 or 2 is acceptable）</string>
    <string name="other_setting">Other</string>
    <string name="adjust_not_tip">Do not display the adjustment completion prompt</string>
    <string name="adjust_not_tip_summary">When turned on, when the box selects the area to complete the translation or adjusts the position of the completed translation result, the prompt text will not pop up</string>
    <string name="init_error">Initialization Failed：%s</string>
    <string name="madoka_newyear">Madoka（New Year）</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="loading_model">Load model</string>
    <string name="model_load_failed">Model load failed：%s</string>
    <string name="rename">Rename</string>
    <string name="confirm_deletion">Confirm Deletion</string>
    <string name="delete_description">Are you sure you want to delete model %1$s? This operation is irreversible.</string>
    <string name="deleteing">Deleting...</string>
    <string name="delete_failed">Delete failed：%s</string>
    <string name="delete_success">Delete successfully</string>
    <string name="rename_tip">Please don’t give too weird names.</string>
    <string name="import_model_dialog_title">Import model</string>
    <string name="import_model_folder_message">Fill in the name of the model you want to import below, then <font color="#E25A5C">go to the folder containing the \".model3.json\" file for the model</font> in the file manager and click the \"Use this folder\" button at the bottom of the screen.\n\nYou can click the \"View Tutorial\" button below for more detailed information (such as the infrastructure of Live2D model files, and the issue that some models cannot be played after importing emoticons and actions, etc.).</string>
    <string name="model_name">Enter a model name...</string>
    <string name="import_success">Import successful</string>
    <string name="import_failed">Import failed：%s</string>


</resources>